[Screen shows phone contact list. User dials 1 866-733-5924.]
Automated Voice: We are unable to complete your call. To speak to a customer service representative, please hang up and dial star 6 1 1.
Automated Voice: Announcement 3. We are unable to com—
[Call disconnects. User returns to contacts and dials 1 562-867-7999.]
Automated Voice: We are unable to complete your call. To speak to a customer service representative, please hang up and dial star 6 1 1.
Automated Voice: Announcement 3. We are unable to com—
[Call disconnects. User returns to contacts and dials (661) 942-2391.]
Automated Voice: Your call cannot be completed as dialed. Please check the number and dial again. Announcement 4. Your call cannot—
[Call disconnects. User returns to contacts and dials 1 248-434-5508.]
[Call connects. Rick Astley's "Never Gonna Give You Up" plays loudly over the phone line.]
[Call disconnects. Screen goes black.]